[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Judd Apatow and Paul Feig created this American comedy series, which contained only 18 episodes.", "correct_answer": "Freaks and Geeks", "incorrect_answers": ["Californication", "Ed", "Nip/Tuck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The life span of a Tomato Frog is 15-35 years.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On January 31, 2008, China announced that it will recycle these to resurface roads.", "correct_answer": "Robbie Williams Cds", "incorrect_answers": ["Old  cars", "Coal", "Old  tires"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 8 Mile, in the first rap off B-Rabbit choked at the mic. What was the name of the guy that beat him in the rap off?", "correct_answer": "Lil Tic", "incorrect_answers": ["Lotto", "Lickity Split", "Papa Doc"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these medical terms refers to air passages in the lungs?", "correct_answer": "Bronchial tubes", "incorrect_answers": ["Neurons", "Axons", "Terminals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is considered that the consumption of these animals transmitted a predecessor of HIV to humans.", "correct_answer": "Primates", "incorrect_answers": ["Birds of prey", "Rats", "Wild animals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actors playing the supporting roles of Angelo Maggio and Alma Burke in this movie received Academy Awards.", "correct_answer": "From Here to Eternity", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bridge on the RIve Kwai", "Around the world in 80 Days", "An American in Paris"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals is NOT native to Australia?", "correct_answer": "Dingo", "incorrect_answers": ["Frilled-neck lizard", "Kangaroo", "Bilby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the beginning of the new millennium New Zealand, Australia and the UK were among the countries with highest consumption of cannabis.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following are among the top female comedy writers in British television?", "correct_answer": "Saunders and French", "incorrect_answers": ["Edie and Patsy", "Judi Dench and Patricia Rutledge", "Stephanie and Holly Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Spiral Island, a small Mexican artificial floating island, was situated on the coast of which sea?", "correct_answer": "The Caribbean Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["The Black Sea", "The Aegean Sea", "The North Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Chris Adams in the third sequel to The Magnificent Seven, The Magnificent Seven Ride?", "correct_answer": "Lee Van Cleef", "incorrect_answers": ["Burt Kennedy", "George Kennedy", "Yul Brynner"]}]